{
	"test": [
		{
			"number": 1,
			"question": "At a local yoga studio, 80% of the members are women and 20% of the members are men. The average age of the women is 30 and the average age of the men is 40.\n\n What is the average age of all the members?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": ["30", "32", "33", "35"],
			"answer": "32"
		},
		{
			"number": 2,
			"question": "Calculate the value of x for the right triangle shown above.",
			"graphic": "Math_Quiz_3_1",
			"answers": ["66", "89", "56", "65"],
			"answer": "65"
		},
		{
			"number": 3,
			"question": "Each player on the high school football team has been weighed, and the data are shown in the box-and-whisker plot above. \n\nBased on this box-and-whisker plot, which of the following statements is accurate?",
			"graphic": "Math_Quiz_3_2",
			"answers": [
				"The heaviest player weighs 300 lbs.",
				"One-fourth of the players weigh less than 200 lbs.",
				"The median player weighs 245 lbs.",
				"The lightest player weighs 200 lbs."
			],
			"answer": "One-fourth of the players weigh less than 200 lbs."
		},
		{
			"number": 4,
			"question": "Each time they play a game there is a 90% chance that the Blue Comets soccer team will score the first goal. What is the probability of the Blue Comets scoring the first goal in 4 straight games?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": ["0.81", "0.45", "0.729", "0.656"],
			"answer": "0.656"
		},
		{
			"number": 5,
			"question": "Calculate the surface area of this soup can. The height of the can is 6 inches and the diameter of the lid is 3 inches.",
			"graphic": "Math_Quiz_3_3",
			"answers": [
				"14.13 inches squared",
				"56.52 inches squared",
				"70.65 inches squared",
				"169.56 inches squared"
			],
			"answer": "169.56 inches squared"
		},
		{
			"number": 6,
			"question": "Charlie lives halfway between Chicago and Hoopertown. Amanda lives halfway between Charlie and Chicago. Raymond lives between Charlie and Hoopertown. All three houses lie on a straight line from Chicago to Hoopertown. \n\nIf Raymond lives 15 miles from Amanda and 23 miles from Chicago, how far does he live from Hoopertown?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": ["5 miles", "7 miles", "9 miles", "12 miles"],
			"answer": "9 miles"
		},
		{
			"number": 7,
			"question": "What is the slope of the line that passes through points (0,5) and (7,0) on the coordinate plane shown above?",
			"graphic": "Math_Quiz_3_4",
			"answers": ["-(7/5)", "-(5/7)", "5/7", "7/5"],
			"answer": "-(5/7)"
		},
		{
			"number": 8,
			"question": "Which of the following equations represents y in terms of x for all ordered pairs listed?",
			"graphic": "Math_Quiz_3_5",
			"answers": ["y = 4x / 3", "y = 2x + 3", "y = x + 5", "y = 3x * 2"],
			"answer": "y = 2x + 3"
		},
		{
			"number": 9,
			"question": "If x is a small negative integer and y is a large positive integer, which of the following expressions must be positive?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": ["x * y", "y - x", "y / x", "x / y"],
			"answer": "y - x"
		},
		{
			"number": 10,
			"question": "Li wants to buy as many bags of mulch as possible with his $305, and he would like them to be delivered to his house. The cost is $7.50 per bag and there is a $35.75 delivery charge. The mulch is only sold in full bags.\n\n How many bags can Li buy?",
			"graphic": "noone",
			"answers": ["35", "36", "45", "46"],
			"answer": "35"
		}
	]
}
